Mojo Spy
Mojo Mojo Mojo Spy
This world is a riot of color, truth and lies beguile our eyes
Use your heart to see clearly, the truth is not far away
Hey you good or bad, truth or lies, can't escape the soul's gray smoke
Bring all your courage, and maybe you can save this world
Mojo Spy
The museum curator refused police help
He used the security system to catch the flea who came to steal the Eternal Flame
But Dorothy created a diversion
and stole the Eternal Flame herself
The Eternal Flame
Mr. Curator
Feeling better?
The Eternal Flame...
Mr. Curator
I'm sorry
The ancient sword, the Eternal Flame
has been stolen by The Illumin-Eye
Fortunately
you were just hypnotized
The doctor said
after a few more hours of rest
you'll fully recover
I hope from now on
You've cooperated closely with us
to take down the Illumin-Eye together
You have something to say?
Back to the museum. Now.
Didn't we just come from there?
Why the rush to get back?
I'll tell you once we get there
What are we looking for?
The Eternal Flame
Could this be the real one?
The curator just told me
what was stolen was only a replica
And the real ancient sword
ever since his grandfather's time
has been sealed behind this wall
This secret
was passed down by word of mouth to the eldest son of each generation
Too bad the curator never expected
the secret would only last three generations
before he had to tell us
What do you mean?
The curator has already agreed
to let us protect the ancient sword?
Yeah. He's fully realized how powerful the Illumin-Eye is
So he agreed
Inspector Sima
Yes.
Take your men immediately
to escort this ancient sword
to the Tuna Town Bank vault and seal it in secret.
Once the Illumin-Eye realizes it got a fake,
it will strike back at once.
So we must move the sword immediately.
Yes, sir.
Stop spacing out.
Hurry.
On it.
Locky,
you and Jingjing haven't slept all night.
Go home and rest.
The case is reaching a boiling point.
And you're actually trying to send me away?
No way.
This kid... I'm so angry my insides hurt. Ouch!
Alright, alright.
You use this every time. So fake.
Stop acting.
Fine, I'll go back.
Jingjing, let's go.
Ouch, that hurts.
I'm going back now.
Okay, thanks for your help, Hawxing.
Looks like The Illumin-Eye's plan this time...
It's not so easy to succeed anymore.
You must have worked really hard.
This is all thanks to your help, Jimmy.
Hmm, I want to ask you again.
Take me to see Mr. K.
Why see him?
Last time he said the power of the Illumin-Eye.
It comes from an ancient book called The Illumin Doctrine.
We have to get our hands on it.
So I wanted to get some intel from him.
It's dawn.
Hey, why are you following us?
Locky
Do you also think something's wrong with Mr. K?
Shaker sent me an email.
She advised me to drop this investigation.
Otherwise, it could be life-threatening.
I suspect that right now, the Illumin-Eye...
We're executing a meticulous, massive plan.
Officer Han said over 90% of the people on the list...
They're all people the police have always suspected.
So.
The list Mr. K gave up
was completely useless.
And the Illumin-Eye's hideout
was empty.
The ancient book he mentioned
was nowhere to be found.
Yeah.
So far he hasn't given us
even a single piece
of useful intel.
Isn't this just a fake surrender?
But the police still seem willing
to trust Mr. K.
I have all kinds of doubts
but can't find any proof.
We can cooperate.
Huh? What did you say?
Let's cooperate to find out the truth.
Oh, did your circuits fry?
My circuits are in perfect condition.
This is the best plan from my computer analysis.
What's your answer?
I'm in a good mood today.
I'll agree to it.
What is this?
Walkie-talkie. Use it to contact me if anything comes up.
Ah, are you out of your mind!
Be careful!
My dear Dorothy,
The sword you found is not the Eternal Flame.
What? But how?
Without a lighthouse, how can a fishing boat return on a rainy night?
The Illumin Doctrine says,
the true Eternal Flame,
when touched by a brave and noble man,
will make the blade's bright patterns glow like fire.
But this sword,
is dim and lifeless.
It must be a fake.
But,
I took this out of the museum with my own hands!
I'm afraid the real sword was already moved.
Enough.
You should take a good rest.
My Lord Eye,
I've made you unhappy again.
Please punish me.
Rothy,
the other day you brought
the only one not destroyed.
Colitas, the Male Flower
I'm already very happy
Let's just forget it this time
You... really don't blame me?
My dear and
devout follower
Actually, I've already sent Shaker
to find Mr. K
The true Eternal Flame
will soon be brought
before us
Ali, Aliba, Aliba is a happy young man~
Can you be quiet for a bit?
Ali
Aliba, Aliba is a happy young man~
Aliba
Aliba is a happy you—th!
Mr. K
Long time no see
Ah, no!
Help!
Don't shoot
She's over there
Ending theme